[
    {
        "question" : "What was the title of the first Apple Explained video?",
        "choice1" : "A. Every Mac Startup and Crash Chime",
        "choice2" : "B. 'O8 MacBook Keynote",
        "choice3" : "C. Don't Compare Apple's HomePod to Amazon's Echo",
        "choice4" : "D. Every Apple Watch Band Ever Made",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "1"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When was the first version of the video 'History of the iPhone released?",
        "choice1" : "A. March 8, 2017",
        "choice2" : "B. August 2, 2019",
        "choice3" : "C. January 22, 2016",
        "choice4" : "D. December 8, 2018",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "2"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "What is the last video Apple Explained posted for 2019?",
        "choice1" : "A. Why Apple Killed 3D Touch",
        "choice2" : "B. Apple's 'Pro' Problem",
        "choice3" : "C. History of the Fifth Avenue Apple Store",
        "choice4" : "D. History of Apple's Website",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "3"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "When did Apple Explained join YouTube?",
        "choice1" : "A. August 30, 2008",
        "choice2" : "B. July 6, 2008",
        "choice3" : "C. March 14, 2007",
        "choice4" : "D. December 2, 2007",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "4"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Apple Explained hit 100,000 subscribers?",
        "choice1" : "A. October 14, 2018",
        "choice2" : "B. April 6, 2018",
        "choice3" : "C. September 11, 2017",
        "choice4" : "D. February 4, 2017",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "5"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "What was the name of the first non-Apple related video posted by Apple Explained on YouTube?",
        "choice1" : "A. What's Going On With Huawei?",
        "choice2" : "B. Why Is Android So Fragmented?",
        "choice3" : "C. 10 Things The Internet Has Destroyed",
        "choice4" : "D. Why Samsung Has Ditched The Headphone Jack",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "6"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "What were the names of the people that founded Apple?",
        "choice1" : "A. Daniel C, Jim Veens, Gregory Wyatt Jr.",
        "choice2" : "B. Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak, Ronald Wayne",
        "choice3" : "C. Kim Jong-Il, Kim Jong-Un",
        "choice4" : "D. Bill Gates, Melinda Gates",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "7"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "Which of the following companies is a subsidiary of Apple?",
        "choice1" : "A. Akapella Interaktive",
        "choice2" : "B. Pixar",
        "choice3" : "C. Netflix",
        "choice4" : "D. Beats Electronics",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "8"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "When was the Apple Explained Discord server **re**made?",
        "choice1" : "A. March 7, 2019",
        "choice2" : "B. February 1, 2019",
        "choice3" : "C. February 9, 2019",
        "choice4" : "D. April 2, 2019",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "9"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "When did the Apple Explained Discord server hit 1000 members?",
        "choice1" : "A. March 14, 2020",
        "choice2" : "B. April 30, 2020",
        "choice3" : "C. July 7, 2020",
        "choice4" : "D. May 12, 2020",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "10"
      }, 
      {
        "question" : "When was Apple founded?",
        "choice1" : "A. April 1, 1976",
        "choice2" : "B. April 30, 1976",
        "choice3" : "C. March 29, 1976",
        "choice4" : "D. February 21, 1976",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "11"
      },
      {
        "question" : "How many (approximate) Apple Stores are there as of 2019?",
        "choice1" : "A. 600",
        "choice2" : "B. 1000",
        "choice3" : "C. 500",
        "choice4" : "D. 5000",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "12"
      },
      {
        "question" : "How many (approximate) employees are working at Apple as of 2019?",
        "choice1" : "A. 200,000",
        "choice2" : "B. 137,000",
        "choice3" : "C. 99,900",
        "choice4" : "D. 91,000",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "13"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Budget Darth Vader (tommystefanatic) begin work on the game commands?",
        "choice1" : "A. May 3, 2020",
        "choice2" : "B. May 2, 2020",
        "choice3" : "C. May 1, 2020",
        "choice4" : "D. May 4, 2020",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "14"
      },
      {
        "question" : "What was the name of Steve Jobs' new company after he left Apple?",
        "choice1" : "A. PrEVIOUS",
        "choice2" : "B. Akapella Komputers",
        "choice3" : "C. NeXT",
        "choice4" : "D. Derpi Industries",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "15"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Gordon get banned from the server?",
        "choice1" : "A. December 10, 2019",
        "choice2" : "B. March 15, 2020",
        "choice3" : "C. February 21, 2020",
        "choice4" : "D. January 29, 2020",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "16"
      },
      {
        "question" : "What was the reasoning for Gordon's ban **literally** according to Apple Moderator?",
        "choice1" : "A. 'abuse of mod power'",
        "choice2" : "B. 'undefined'",
        "choice3" : "C. 'messing around with .say'",
        "choice4" : "D. 'just a test ban'",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "17"
      },
      {
        "question" : "What was the sanity check phrase for .clearwarn?",
        "choice1" : "A. YES I WANT TO DO IT",
        "choice2" : "B. I AM NOT CRAZY, DO IT",
        "choice3" : "C. CHECK ME FOR DRUG ABUSE, I DON'T HAVE ANY, DO IT",
        "choice4" : "D. YES I AM SURE",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "18"
      },
      {
        "question" : "What's the name of Tommy Stefanos' girlfriend?",
        "choice1" : "A. Anna Hardy",
        "choice2" : "B. Stephanie Alderney",
        "choice3" : "C. Samantha Cook",
        "choice4" : "D. Christine Michaels",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "19"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Tommy Stefanos get the Apple User role?",
        "choice1" : "A. January 27, 2020",
        "choice2" : "B. February 3, 2020",
        "choice3" : "C. December 31, 2019",
        "choice4" : "D. March 1, 2020",
        "answer" : "b",
        "answer_case" : "B",
        "qid" : "20"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Derpi first join the server?",
        "choice1" : "A. November 27, 2019",
        "choice2" : "B. October 3, 2019",
        "choice3" : "C. December 31, 2019",
        "choice4" : "D. September 12, 2019",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "21"
      },
      {
        "question" : "When did Jim Veens get moderator status?",
        "choice1" : "A. April 26, 2020",
        "choice2" : "B. April 3, 2020",
        "choice3" : "C. March 28, 2020",
        "choice4" : "D. February 2, 2020",
        "answer" : "d",
        "answer_case" : "D",
        "qid" : "22"
      },
      {
        "question" : "What is Daniel's GitHub username?",
        "choice1" : "A. TechGeekGamer",
        "choice2" : "B. ihavenothingtodobutcode",
        "choice3" : "C. BowBeforeMe420",
        "choice4" : "D. H4ck3rMuch",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "23"
      },
      {
        "question" : "Since what year was Bootcamp introduced on Macs?",
        "choice1" : "A. 2004",
        "choice2" : "B. 2013",
        "choice3" : "C. 2006",
        "choice4" : "D. 2008",
        "answer" : "c",
        "answer_case" : "C",
        "qid" : "24"
      },
      {
        "question" : "The OS X to macOS name transition occured at what version of macOS?",
        "choice1" : "A. Sierra",
        "choice2" : "B. Mavericks",
        "choice3" : "C. El Capitan",
        "choice4" : "D. Catalina",
        "answer" : "a",
        "answer_case" : "A",
        "qid" : "25"
      }
]